Guide to the World War II Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- GENERAL PUBLICATIONS, Series I
  - United States
    - Civil rights (Box 25, Folder 295)
    - Civilian defense (Box 25, Folder 296-297)
      - Baltimore, Maryland (Box 26, Folder 298)
      - Boston, Massachusetts (Box 26, Folder 299)
      - Charleston, South Carolina (Box 26, Folder 300)
      - Connecticut (Box 26, Folder 301)
      - Illinois (Box 26, Folder 302)
      - Los Angeles, California (Box 26, Folder 303)
      - New Hampshire (Box 26, Folder 304)
      - New Jersey (Box 26, Folder 305)
      - New York (City) (Box 26, Folder 306-307)
      - Norfolk, Virginia (Box 26, Folder 308)
      - Ohio (Box 26, Folder 309)
      - San Diego, California (Box 26, Folder 310)
      - San Francisco, California (Box 26, Folder 311)
      - Seattle, Washington (Box 27, Folder 312)
    - Conscientious objectors
      - Association of Catholic Conscientious Objectors (Box 27, Folder 313)
      - Civilian Public Service Camps, nos. 37, 53 (Box 27, Folder 313)
      - Disciples of Christ (Box 27, Folder 313)
      - Mennonite Central Committee (Box 27, Folder 314)
      - National Service Board for Religious Objectors (Box 27, Folder 314)
      - War Resisters League (Box 27, Folder 315)
    - Conscription (Box 27, Folder 316)
    - Economic aspects (Box 27, Folder 317)
    - Education (Box 27, Folder 318)
    - Food (Box 27, Folder 319)
      - Government reports
        - Office of Strategic Services. Mediterranean Section. Coordinator of Information. The Railroads of West and Central Africa. Vol. 1 (Part 8 of C.O.I.'s Monograph No. 4), 1942 March 26 (Box 27A)
        - Office of Strategic Services. Research and Analysis Branch. African Section. Transafrican Overland Routes: Ports Railroads, Rivers and Lakes, Roads. Report No. 54, 1942 July 2 (Box 27B)
        - Office of Strategic Services. Research and Analysis Branch. Morocco. Vol. 1, 1942 August 3 (Box 27C)
    - Humor (Box 27, Folder 320)
    - Industry - Advertising, news releases, etc. (Box 27, Folder 321-322)
    - Industry - Advertising, news releases, etc. (Box 28, Folder 323-324)
      - Posters (Box 28, Folder 323-324)
        See box 50
    - Industry - Memorabilia (Box 28, Folder 325)
    - International affairs (Treatises) (Box 28, Folder 326-327)
      - Far East (Box 28, Folder 328)
      - Germany (Box 28, Folder 329-330)
    - Japanese - Relocation, war service (Box 29, Folder 331)
    - Legislation (Box 29, Folder 332)
    - Local history (Box 29, Folder 333)
      - New Haven War Bond Drive, 1942 Sep 24 (Box 29, Folder 334)
    - Media (Box 29, Folder 335)
    - Merchant Marine (Box 29, Folder 336)
    - Peace - Individuals (Box 29, Folder 337)
    - Peace - Organizations (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Church Peace Union and World Alliance for International Friendship (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Churchmen's Committee for a Christian Peace (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Commission to Study the Organization of the Peace (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Congregational Christian Study of World Organizations (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Episcopal Pacifist Fellowship (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Federal Council of the Churches of Christ in America (Box 29, Folder 338)
      - Friends' Peace Committee (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - Methodist Church (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - National Council for Prevention of War (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - National Study Conference on the Churches and a Just and Durable Peace (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - Peace Assembly of the City Council of Youth, Cleveland (Box 29, Folder 339)
      - Peace Now Movement (Box 30, Folder 340)
      - Peoples Mandate Committee for Inter-American Peace and Cooperation (Box 30, Folder 341)
      - Post War World Council (Box 30, Folder 342)
      - War Resisters League (Box 30, Folder 342)
      - World Peace movements (Box 30, Folder 342)
      - [Fellowship of Reconciliation?] (Box 30, Folder 342)
      - Unnamed committee. Study Pamphlet of the War ... (Box 30, Folder 342)
    - Personal narratives/Miller, Henry. Murder the Murders (Box 30, Folder 343)
    - Political organizations - General
      - Miscellaneous groups A - M (Box 30, Folder 344)
      - Miscellaneous groups N - Z (Box 30, Folder 345)
      - Citizens for Victory (Box 30, Folder 346)
      - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies (Box 30, Folder 347)
      - Committee for a Democratic Foreign Policy (Box 30, Folder 348)
      - League for Fair Play (Box 30, Folder 349)
      - Union for Democratic Action (Box 30, Folder 350)
      - Writers' War Board (Box 30, Folder 351)
    - Political organizations - By locality
      - Re: Germany (Box 31, Folder 352)
        - American Association for a Democratic Germany (Box 31, Folder 352)
        - American Friends of German Freedom (Box 31, Folder 353)
        - German-American Bund (Box 31, Folder 354)
        - Reichsdeutsche Vereinigung Gross - New York Transatlantica (Box 31, Folder 354)
      - Re: Greece (Box 31, Folder 355)
        - Greek American Committee for National Unity (Box 31, Folder 355)
        - Greek American Council (Box 31, Folder 355)
        - Greek-American Labor Committee (Box 31, Folder 355)
      - Re: Hungary (Box 31, Folder 356)
        - American Hungarian Federation (Box 31, Folder 356)
        - Movement for Independent Hungary (Box 31, Folder 356)
        - New York Council of Hungarian Americans for Victory (Box 31, Folder 356)
      - Re: India
        - Free India Committee (Box 31, Folder 357)
        - Friends of Freedom for India (Box 31, Folder 357)
        - National Committee for India's Freedom (Box 31, Folder 357)
        - India League of America (Box 31, Folder 358)
      - Re: Ireland (Box 31, Folder 359)
        - American Irish Defense Organization (Box 31, Folder 359)
        - Committee for American Irish Defense (Box 31, Folder 359)
      - Re: Italy/ Mazzini Society et al. (Box 31, Folder 360)
      - Re: Korea (Box 31, Folder 361)
        - Korean Civic Association (Box 31, Folder 361)
        - Sino-Korean People's League (Box 31, Folder 361)
      - Re: Poland (Box 32, Folder 362)
        See also: box 20, folders 233-234 box 21, folder 238
        - American Committee to Honor the Polish Navy and Merchant Marine (Box 32, Folder 362)
        - American-Polish National Council (Box 32, Folder 362)
        - Polish National Council (Box 32, Folder 362)
      - Re: Romania (Box 32, Folder 362A)
      - Re: Russia
        - American Council on Soviet Relations (Box 32, Folder 363)
        - National Council of American Soviet Friendship (Box 32, Folder 364)
        - Russian-American National Committee (Box 32, Folder 365)
      - Re: Scandinavia - American Scandinavian Committee (Box 32, Folder 366)
      - Re: Yugoslavia
        - United Committee of South-Slavic Americans (Box 32, Folder 367-368)
        - National Committee of American Airmen: "A Partial Collection of Press Clippings to Aid General Draza Mihailovic", 1946 (Box 32, Folder 368A)
    - Postwar aims (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - American Friends of German Freedom. Germany Tomorrow (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Buck, Pearl S. Freedom for All (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Butler, Nicholas Murray. Liberty, Equality and Fraternity (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Carman, Harry J. Academic Research and the Quest for Peace (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Dulles, John Foster. Long Range Peace Objectives (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Woodward, Carl R. The Quest for Liberty and Unity (Box 32, Folder 369)
    - Postwar planning (Box 32, Folder 369)
      - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace. After the War (Box 32, Folder 370)
      - Commission on World Peace. When Hostilities Cease (Box 32, Folder 370)
      - Culbertson, Ely. The World Federation Plan (Box 32, Folder 370)
      - Gilbert, Felix and Holborn, Hajo. American Policy with Regard to Post-War Germany (Box 32, Folder 370)
      - Harvard Council on Post-War Problems. Understanding Victory (Box 32, Folder 371)
      - Hickenlooper, Bourke, Post-War Military Policy (Box 32, Folder 371)
      - National Peace Conference. World Government (Box 32, Folder 371)
      - Van Zeeland, Paul. Which Path Will the World Follow After the War? (Box 32, Folder 371)
      - Von Mises, Ludwig. An Eastern Democratic Union (Box 32, Folder 371)
      - World Peace Foundation. American Policy Toward Japan ... (Box 32, Folder 371)
    - Postwar policy
      - Germany (Box 32, Folder 372)
      - Japan - German language (Box 32, Folder 373)
    - Propaganda
      - Miscellaneous (Box 32, Folder 374)
      - For Philippines - In English and Tagalog languages (Box 32, Folder 375)
      - For Slavic peoples - English language (Box 32, Folder 376)
      - Spanish language (Box 32, Folder 377)
      - Free World Association. Texts of 61 radio broadcasts to Europe and 1 to China, 1941 July - 1942 April (Box 32A, Folder 377a-f)
    - Public opinion (Box 33, Folder 378)
      - Anti-war (Box 33, Folder 379)
      - On Germany (Box 33, Folder 380)
      - On Japan (Box 33, Folder 381)
    - Refugees (Box 33, Folder 382)
      - Joint Anti-fascist Refugee Committee (Box 33, Folder 383)
      - Selfhelp of Emigres from Central Europe (Box 33, Folder 384)
    - Religious aspects (Box 34, Folder 385-386)
    - Segregation in the Armed forces: Lynn Committee (Box 34, Folder 387)
    - Veterans (Box 34, Folder 388)
    - War aims (Box 34, Folder 389)
    - War crimes and trials (Box 34, Folder 390)
    - War effort (Box 34, Folder 391)
    - War histories (Box 34, Folder 392)
    - War histories - Reports (Box 34, Folder 393)
      - Marshall, George C. "The Winning of the War in Europe and the Pacific." Biennial Report of the Chief of Staff President's Commission. "Attack Upon Pearl Harbor by Japanese Armed Forces,", 1942 January 23 (Box 34, Folder 393)
      - U.S. Strategic Bombing Survey. "Japan's Struggle to End the War,", 1946 July 1 (Box 34, Folder 393)
    - War literature - Memoirs (Box 34, Folder 394)
    - War relief - General
      - Miscellaneous groups A - M (Box 34, Folder 395)
      - Miscellaneous groups N - Z (Box 34, Folder 396)
      - American Red Cross (Box 34, Folder 397)
      - Bundles for America (Box 35, Folder 398)
      - Committee for the Care of European Children (Box 35, Folder 399)
      - Community War Fund (Box 35, Folder 400)
      - International Rescue and Relief Committee (Box 35, Folder 401)
      - National Committee on Food for the Small Democracies (Box 35, Folder 402)
      - National War Fund (Box 35, Folder 403)
      - Save the Children Federation (Box 35, Folder 404)
      - Temporary Council on Food for Europe's Children (Box 35, Folder 405)
      - Unitarian Service Committee (Box 35, Folder 406)
      - United Service Organization (Box 35, Folder 407)
    - War relief - By locality
      - Belgium (Box 35, Folder 408)
        - Belgians in Britain (Box 35, Folder 409)
      - China (Box 35, Folder 410)
        - American Committee for Chinese Industrial Cooperatives (Box 35, Folder 411)
      - Finland (Box 35, Folder 412)
        - Finnish Relief Fund (Box 35, Folder 412)
        - For Finland (Box 35, Folder 412)
      - France (Box 35, Folder 413)
        - American Relief for France (Box 35, Folder 414)
        - Coordinating Council for French Relief Societies (Box 35, Folder 415)
      - Great Britain (Box 36, Folder 416)
        - American Committee for Defense of British Homes (Box 36, Folder 417)
        - American Labor Committee to Aid British Labor (Box 36, Folder 418)
        - Bundles for Britain (Box 36, Folder 419)
      - Greece (Box 36, Folder 420)
        - Greek War Relief Association (Box 36, Folder 421)
      - Jews (Box 36, Folder 422)
      - Netherlands (Box 36, Folder 423)
      - Norway (Box 36, Folder 424)
      - Philippines (Box 36, Folder 425)
      - Poland (Box 36, Folder 426)
        - Commission for Polish Relief (Box 36, Folder 426)
        - Paderewski Fund for Polish Relief (Box 36, Folder 426)
        - Polish War Fund (Box 36, Folder 426)
      - Russia/ Russian War Relief (Box 36, Folder 427)
      - Spain (Box 36, Folder 428)
      - Yugoslavia (Box 36, Folder 429)
        - American Committee for Yugoslav Relief (Box 36, Folder 430)
    - War relief - Reports (Box 36, Folder 431)
      - "Voluntary War Relief During World War II." A report to the President's War Relief Control Board, 1946 March (Box 36, Folder 431)
    - Women (Box 36, Folder 432)
    - World government (Box 36, Folder 433)
      - World Government Association (Box 36, Folder 434)
    - Youth movements (Box 36, Folder 435)
      - American Student Union (Box 36, Folder 436)
  - United Nations (Box 22, Folder 256)
  - UNRRA - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Agency (Box 22, Folder 257)
    Posters - See Folio 50
  - Yugoslavia
    - English language (Box 37, Folder 437)
      See also: box 32, folders 367-368 box 36, folder 429
      - Memorandum of the Government of the Federative People's Republic of Yugoslavia on Slovene Carinthia, the Slovene frontier areas of Styria and the Croats of Burgenland (includes annexes nos. 1-6) (Box 37, Folder 438)
      - Publications of the Royal Yugoslav Government (Box 37, Folder 439)
    - French language (Box 37, Folder 440)
    - German language (Box 37, Folder 441)
  - Source unidentified (Box 37, Folder 442)
- LEAFLETS, NEWSPAPERS AND REPORTS, Series II
  - Leaflets
    - Allied Force Headquarters/ European Campaign - English language (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Allied Command
      - European Campaign
        - To European civilians (French, Alsatians, Luxemburgers, etc.) (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - For German troops (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - For Germany (foreign workers) - German and other languages (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - For Germany (workers and civilians) - German language (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Italian Campaign
        - German language - for Austrian troops (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - German language - with English translations (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Italian language - for Italian troops (Box 38, Folder 8)
          see: box 39, folder 15
        - Italian language - for Italian troops (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - North African Campaign
        - German language - for Austrian troops (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - German language - for German troops (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - Italian language - for Italian troops (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Allied Force Headquarters
      - Psychological Warfare Branch
        - Propaganda evaluation (Box 38, Folder 13)
          see: box 41, folder 50
        - Reports - March 1943 - 30 April 1943 - with sample leaflets (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - Reports - 10 May 1943 - 15 June 1943 - with sample leaflets (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - Reports - 1 July - 1 September 1943 - with sample leaflets (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Reports - 1 October 1943 - 1 February 1944 - with sample leaflets (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Printer's proofs of headlines [?] (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - France
      - For France - DeGaulle, Vichy (Box 39, Folder 19)
      - For French in Germany (Box 39, Folder 20)
      - For German Army (Box 39, Folder 21)
      - For Tunisia (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - France - Communist Party - for France (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Germany
      - For Americans (Box 39, Folder 24)
      - For Austria (Box 39, Folder 25)
      - For British civilians (Box 39, Folder 26)
      - For France (Box 39, Folder 27)
      - For North African Campaign - Arabic, French language (Box 39, Folder 28)
    - Great Britain
      - Arabic (Box 39, Folder 29)
      - For Austria (Box 40, Folder 30)
      - Propaganda abroad - Chinese language (Box 40, Folder 31)
      - Czech language (Box 40, Folder 32)
      - Dutch language (Box 40, Folder 33)
      - English language (Box 40, Folder 34)
      - Posters - English language - Used in Life, 18 Mar 1940 (Box 40, Folder 35)
      - Airplane propaganda, leaflets - Flemish (Box 40, Folder 36)
      - French language (Box 40, Folder 37)
      - German language (Box 40, Folder 38)
      - German language (Box 40, Folder 39)
      - Hungarian language (Box 40, Folder 40)
      - Hungarian (Box 40, Folder 41)
      - Italian language (Box 40, Folder 42)
      - Norwegian (Box 40, Folder 43)
      - Polish language (Box 40, Folder 44)
      - Portuguese language (Box 40, Folder 45)
      - Spanish language (Box 41, Folder 46)
    - Japan - English language - for Americans, Australians, Filipinos (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Japan - Chinese language - for Chinese (Box 41, Folder 47)
    - Nationalkomitee freies Deutschland - to German Army (Box 41, Folder 48)
    - Russia
      - To German Army (Box 41, Folder 49)
      - European Campaign (Box 41, Folder 49)
        - Re: German language leaflet series numbered 1 - 14D - English paraphrase and analysis by Psychological Warfare Branch (Box 41, Folder 50)
        - German language - leaflets number 1 - 6K (Box 41, Folder 51)
        - German language - leaflets number 7A - 11 (Box 41, Folder 52)
        - German language - leaflets number 13A - 13H for Newspapers - 14A - 14D (Box 41, Folder 53)
          see: Folio 49
        - Front-Illustrierte, No. 2 - Jan. 1942
        - Front-Illustrierte, No. 5 - March (Box 41, Folder 53)
        - Soldatenzeitung, No. 26 - 25 November 1941 (Box 41, Folder 53)
        - Soldatenzeitung-Sonderausgabe, No. 7 - Christmas 1941. (Box 41, Folder 53)
        - Die Wahrheit, February 1942, March 1942 (Box 41, Folder 53)
        - Das Freie Wort, No. 6 - 10 February 1942 (Box 41, Folder 53)
          See: Folio 49
        - German language - leaflets number 12A - 12U (Box 41, Folder 54)
      - Over Iran - Persian, Armenian, French (Box 41, Folder 55)
      - For Russians (Box 41, Folder 56-57)
    - United States
      - For Belgium (Box 41, Folder 58)
      - For France (Box 41, Folder 59)
      - For German Army - Austrians (Box 41, Folder 60)
      - For German Army - Russian, Ukrainian, Georgian (Box 41, Folder 61)
      - For German Army in Tunisia (Box 41, Folder 62)
      - For Germany - German Army (Box 41, Folder 63)
      - For civilians and soldiers - Italian language (Box 41, Folder 64)
      - Greek language (Box 41, Folder 65)
      - Japanese language
        - For Japanese (Box 41, Folder 66)
        - For Japanese soldiers (Box 41, Folder 67)
        - For Japanese soldiers - issued in 1942 in the Pacific (Box 41, Folder 68)
        - Leaflets with English translation
          Conditions Governing Access
          The material is available on microfilm. Patrons must use HM 261 instead of the originals.
          - Series J-1
            - Nos. 2-20 (Box 42, Folder 69)
            - Nos. 21-36 (Box 42, Folder 70)
            - Nos. 101-129 (Box 42, Folder 71)
            - Nos. 132-152 (Box 42, Folder 72)
          - Series J-3 (Box 42, Folder 73)
          - Series J-6 (Box 42, Folder 74)
          - Series J-11, J-21 [miscellaneous numbers] (Box 42, Folder 75)
        - Airplane leaflets for Japanese without translation (Box 42, Folder 76-77)
        - Newspapers [some with English translation] (Box 42, Folder 78)
        - Leaflets and newspapers on the fighting in Burma with English translation (Box 42, Folder 79)
        - Leaflets for Formosa with English translation (Box 42, Folder 80)
        - Leaflets for Okinawa - x-series with English translation (Box 42, Folder 81)
      - For North Africa - French and Arabic languages (Box 43, Folder 82)
      - For Norway (Box 43, Folder 83)
      - For South Pacific (Box 43, Folder 84)
      - For Yugoslavia (Box 43, Folder 85)
  - Newspapers
    - Allied Command - News flashes (Box 43, Folder 86)
    - Allied Force Headquarters
      - Afrika-Post (Box 43, Folder 87)
      - Corriere dell 'Aria (Box 43, Folder 88)
      - Corriere Illustrato (Box 43, Folder 89)
      - De Forente Nasjoner - Norwegian and English translations (Box 43, Folder 90)
      - Foglio Volante (Box 43, Folder 91)
      - Frontpost, Nos. 1-14 - 1943 Nov 4 - 1944 Feb 2 (Box 43, Folder 92)
    - Allied Air Forces
      - Harbinger of Freedom (Box 43, Folder 93)
      - L'Amérique en Guerre - French and English translations (Box 43, Folder 94)
      - L'Arc en Ciel - French and English translations (Box 43, Folder 95)
      - De Regenboog - Flemish and English translations (Box 43, Folder 96)
      - De Vliegende Hollander - Dutch and English translations (Box 43, Folder 97)
      - La Vanga (Box 43, Folder 98)
      - Luftpost - German and English translations (Box 43, Folder 99)
      - Le Courier de L'Air - see also: copies dropped as airplane propaganda under "British - For France" - French and English translation (Box 43, Folder 100)
      - Tous les Front - French language (Box 43, Folder 101)
      - Voir - French language (Box 43, Folder 102)
    - Great Britain - New Constitutional Order 1941-1943 (incomplete) - English language/ Union Jack, 1944 July 24 (Box 43, Folder 103)
    - Netherlands
      - Het Parool (Box 43, Folder 104)
      - Trouw (Box 43, Folder 105)
    - United States
      - Stars and Stripes, 1945 July 11, August 22 (Box 43, Folder 106)
    - U.S.I.A.
      - Sternenbanner - German and English translation (Box 43, Folder 107)
    - Nase Noviny - Czech language 1 v., 1944 (Box 43A)
  - Blankenhorn, Heber, collector
    Reports, memoranda, manuals and books written or collected by Lt. Col. Heber Blankenhorn concerning United States psychological warfare operations. Much of the material was produced by the Psychological Warfare Branches of the War Department and the Allied Force Headquarters.
    - Reports
      - Allied Force Headquarters. Psychological Warfare Branch
        - Report on combat propaganda leaflets, 1943-1944 (Box 43B, Folder 108)
        - Blankenhorn, Heber. Soldiers Committees: History of MO Project (Black), 1944-1945, 1945 January (Box 43B, Folder 108)
        - Mimeographed reports, 1943 October 2 -December 27, 1945 July 30 (Box 43B, Folder 109)
      - War Department. Psychological Warfare Branch
        - Blankenhorn, Heber. Combat Propaganda in Africa, Italy, United Kingdom and France, 1946 January (Box 43B, Folder 110-111)
    - Memoranda
      - Great Britain. Home Guard, 1942-1944 (Box 43B, Folder 112)
    - Manuals
      - Allied Force Headquarters. Psychological Warfare Branch
        - Confetti. Combat Propaganda, [1943] (Box 43B, Folder 113)
        - P.W.B. Combat Propaganda, [1943] (Box 43B, Folder 113)
      - Committee for National Morale
        - German Psychological Warfare, 1941 (Box 43B, Folder 113)
      - Fifth Army Headquarters. Psychological Warfare Branch
        - Functions of the Fifth Army Combat Propaganda Team, [1944] (Box 43B, Folder 113)
        - Psychological Warfare Units in the Field, 1944 January 10 (Box 43B, Folder 113)
      - War Department. Military Intelligence Service
        - Intelligence Bulletin. Vol. 1, No. 3, 1942 November (Box 43C, Folder 114)
        - Military Intelligence Propaganda, [1940] (Box 43C, Folder 114)
        - Military Reports, 1944 October (Box 43C, Folder 114)
      - War Department. Military Intelligence Service. Psychological Warfare Branch
        - Training Manual. Combat Propaganda Company, 1942 (Box 43C, Folder 114)
    - Books
      - Second Mobile Radio Broadcasting Co. History. December 1943 - May 1945 (Box 43C, Folder 115)
      - Twelfth United States Army Group. European Theater of Operation. Publicity and Psychological Warfare. January 1943 - August 1945 (Box 43C, Folder 116)
- CIVILIAN CORRESPONDENCE, DIARIES AND MEMORABILIA, Series III
  - Argentine Republic (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Asia - The Far East in the Summer of 1940 (report), [1941] (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Austria, 1937-1940 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Belgian Congo, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Belgium, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - China, 1940-1941 (Box 44, Folder 5)